meet Adam he has built wealth and a
healthy savings that will continue to
give you returns but he doesn't like to
leave things to chance and is
considering to diversify his investments
to better protect his family and his
wealth he comes across son wealth an
insurance savings plan that offers him
wealth protection the flexibility to
choose a payment term he's comfortable
with and just like that he's protected
for the next 25 years more importantly
Sunwell gives great guaranteed benefits
potential returns an insurance
protection for starters Adam is
guaranteed acceptance into the plan even
without a medical check-up every year
while his policy is an effect he will
receive guaranteed cash payout this
means throughout his 25 year plan he
would have received a total payout of up
to six hundred and forty two percent of
his basic annualized premium and when
his policy matures he will also receive
up to two hundred and twenty eight
percent of the basic annualized premium
or the value of the universal account
whichever is higher
plus throughout the twenty five year
plan Adam and his
we'll be protected even if anything
happens to him and because he wants the
best for his family he boosted his
coverage around with an optional term
life rider so you see to Adam son wealth
is perfect as it gives him protection
and potential investment earnings all in
one plan so just like ever
you too can benefit from son wealth a
protection plan that stacks up with
guarantee returns every year and get
your plan at any CIMB Bank brunch nation
you